<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introductions on Indoor Navigation Built with Google Maps</title>
    <link>https://mapsindoors.github.io/introductions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introductions on Indoor Navigation Built with Google Maps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>MapsIndoors (c)2017</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mapsindoors.github.io/introductions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Indoor Positioning with MapsIndoors</title>
      <link>https://mapsindoors.github.io/introductions/indoor-positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mapsindoors.github.io/introductions/indoor-positioning/</guid>
      <description>To get an introduction to the field of indoor positioning, we recommend this blog post for a start.
MapsIndoors SDK is not an IPS (Indoor Positioning Service). MapsIndoors provides indoor maps and indoor directions, and since it is based on Google Maps, we also provide seamless indoor/outdoor integration.
With this in mind you need to find an IPS and then use the location from that IPS in MapsIndoors. To some extend iOS CoreLocation and Android Location Services can fulfill the role of an IPS, depending on the building infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location Sources in MapsIndoors</title>
      <link>https://mapsindoors.github.io/introductions/location-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mapsindoors.github.io/introductions/location-sources/</guid>
      <description>Location Sources is a new feature introduced in version 3 of MapsIndoors SDK for Android and iOS. Basically we are making it possible to register your own custom location data source, adhering to a very simple interface.
The Concepts The central concepts in this feature are Location Sources and Location Observers, and they are best described in the following illustration:
Location Source Maintains an array of locations and notifies its Location Observers about location and status updates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>